export const ai_card_data = [
  {
    title: "Intelligent Conversations",
    body: "The chatbot application leverages state-of-the-art GPT models to provide intelligent, context-aware responses, ensuring engaging and personalized conversations with your customers.",
    icon: "./images/landing/ai_card_data_icon_1.svg",
  },
  {
    title: "Tailored Knowledge Base",
    body: "Stomps is designed to digest and utilize a knowledge base unique to your business, ensuring every response is accurate and perfectly aligned with your specific industry demands.",
    icon: "./images/landing/ai_card_data_icon_2.svg",
  },
  {
    title: "Real-Time Assistance",
    body: "The chatbot offers 24/7 support, instantly addressing multiple queries simultaneously. It dramatically reduces wait times, ensuring customers receive prompt, efficient assistance anytime.",
    icon: "./images/landing/ai_card_data_icon_3.svg",
  },
  {
    title: "Automation of Routine Tasks",
    body: "Stomps excels in handling inquiries and providing quick, accurate FAQs around the clock. By taking over routine questions, it frees your team to focus on more complex tasks. jgjhh",
    icon: "./images/landing/ai_card_data_icon_4.svg",
  },
  {
    title: "Scalability and Adaptability",
    body: "The chatbot effortlessly handles more conversations as your business expands. It ensures you're always equipped to engage your customers, no matter how big you get.ygygig jhbhyg",
    icon: "./images/landing/ai_card_data_icon_5.svg",
  },
  {
    title: "Customization & Personalization",
    body: "Stomps is fully customizable, allowing you to tailor its appearance, feel, and responses to seamlessly align with your brand identity and engage your audience with a truly personalized experience",
    icon: "./images/landing/ai_card_data_icon_6.svg",
  },
  {
    title: "Analytics and Insights",
    body: "The chatbot offers deep analytics on user interactions. Discover your customers' true needs, preferences, and the hurdles they face, enabling data-driven strategies to enhance their experience.",
    icon: "./images/landing/ai_card_data_icon_7.svg",
  },
  {
    title: "Cost Savings",
    body: "The chatbot automates your customer support and routine tasks, enabling your business to save costs associated with hiring additional staff or outsourcing support services.",
    icon: "./images/landing/ai_card_data_icon_8.svg",
  },
];

export const how_it_works = [
  {
    question: "Quick Setup & Host",
    answer:
      "Getting Stomps ready is a breeze. Start by deploying the application on a cloud server of your choice—this is where Stomps lives and operates. Next, sign into your secure dashboard, the command center for all things Stomps. Here, you'll add crucial APIs from Pinecone and OpenAI, enabling Stomps to deliver its magic. Pinecone powers the chatbot's ability to sift through data and understand context, making interactions smarter. OpenAI's API injects cutting-edge language understanding, ensuring Stomps can converse naturally and intelligently. In just a few steps, you're set up and ready to redefine how you engage with your customers.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    question: "Import Data Source",
    answer:
      "Customizing Stomps to serve your needs starts with feeding it the right information directly from your website, key documents, and any text you choose. Whether it’s detailed service descriptions from your site, product manuals in PDF, or policy documents in Word format, Stomps pulls this data into its knowledge base effortlessly. This way, Stomps becomes an expert on your offerings, ready to deliver spot-on, informed responses to your customers.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    question: "Personalize Your Chatbot",
    answer:
      "With Stomps, tailoring your chatbot to embody your brand's essence is straightforward. From injecting your unique tone and language to customizing its appearance, Stomps adapts to fit into your digital landscape. This level of personalization ensures consistency across customer interactions and enhances the overall user experience, making every conversation with the chatbot authentic.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    question: "Embed Your Site",
    answer:
      "Embedding Stomps on your website is designed to be a smooth, hassle-free process. Once Stomps is set up and personalized to your liking, integrating it into your site involves inserting a simple line of code into your webpage's HTML. This code snippet is provided directly within the Stomps dashboard, making it easy to copy and paste into your site, instantly bringing Stomps to life on your platform. Whether you're looking to add Stomps to a specific page for targeted support or across your entire site for comprehensive coverage, this straightforward integration ensures Stomps is ready to engage with your visitors without any heavy lifting from your tech team.",
    open: false,
  },
];

export const your_question_answered = [
  {
    question: "When will Stomps be available?",
    answer:
      "We're working hard to bring Stomps to you as soon as possible, aiming for a launch in the near future. While we're targeting the end of 1st quarter or beginning of second quarter for our release, our commitment is to ensure Stomps meets our high standards of quality and user experience. To stay updated on our progress and get notified the moment Stomps is available, sign up for our mailing list. We appreciate your interest and patience!",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    question: "What does the one-time purchase price of Stomps include?",
    answer:
      "The one-time purchase of Stomps grants you complete access to deploy the software on your chosen cloud provider, ensuring you can start enhancing your customer interactions right away. Plus, it includes an hour of free setup support to help you get up and running smoothly, making onboarding a breeze.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    question: "Are there any recurring fees after the one-time purchase?",
    answer:
      "No, there are no recurring fees with Stomps after your initial purchase. Enjoy ongoing updates that enhance Stomps' functionality, viewable in our changelog. Optional advanced updates may incur a one-time fee, but these are entirely at your discretion, ensuring you only pay for what you need.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    question: "What additional costs should I anticipate?",
    answer:
      "Beyond the one-time purchase of Stomps, anticipate costs related to usage-based fees from Pinecone and OpenAI, as their services power key functionalities of your chatbot. Additionally, one-time fees may apply for specific actions, such as embedding content into the database. You'll also cover cloud hosting costs for your deployment. These external expenses depend on your usage and hosting choices, allowing you to manage and optimize based on your needs.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What roles do Pinecone and OpenAI play in enhancing Stomps, and what are the associated costs?",
    answer:
      "Pinecone and OpenAI are integral to Stomps, providing the advanced search capabilities and natural language processing that make your chatbot intelligent and responsive. Pinecone powers our sophisticated data retrieval, ensuring quick, relevant answers, while OpenAI's GPT technology enables Stomps to understand and generate human-like text. These services operate on usage-based pricing, meaning costs will vary depending on how much you use them.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    question: "How easy is it to set up and deploy Stomps?",
    answer:
      "Setting up and deploying Stomps is designed to be straightforward, ensuring you can get your chatbot up and running quickly. With a simple installation process complemented by dedicated setup support, you'll have Stomps integrated into your website effortlessly. Our dashboard further simplifies customization and management, enabling you to tailor Stomps to your needs seamlessly without any technical headaches.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    question: "Can I customize Stomps to fit my brand?",
    answer:
      "Absolutely! Stomps is designed with customization at its core, allowing you to tailor its appearance, tone, and responses to match your brand identity perfectly. From visual elements to conversational style, Stomps can be adapted to ensure a seamless and branded experience for your customers.",
    open: false,
  },
];

export const plan_data = [
  {
    availability: true,
    tag: "Your Own API Key:",
    text: " Opt for GPT-3.5 or GPT-4, tailoring the AI's power to your needs.",
  },
  {
    availability: true,
    tag: "Unlimited Message Credits:",
    text: "Freely interact with your audience, with no cap on exchanges.",
  },
  {
    availability: true,
    tag: "Unlimited Characters for Embeddings:",
    text: "Process extensive data without limits, perfect for creating rich, nuanced chatbot interactions.",
  },
  {
    availability: true,
    tag: "View Conversation History:",
    text: "Easily access past chats for insights and optimization.",
  },
  {
    availability: true,
    tag: "View Conversation History:",
    text: "Easily access past chats for insights and optimization.",
  },
  {
    availability: true,
    tag: "Upload Multiple Files:",
    text: "Broaden your chatbot’s understanding with diverse document uploads.",
  },
  {
    availability: true,
    tag: "Train on Unlimited Website Links:",
    text: "Enhance its knowledge base by linking to an unlimited number of web pages.",
  },
  {
    availability: true,
    tag: "No 'Powered by Stomps' Branding:",
    text: "Maintain your brand’s integrity without external logos or mentions.",
  },
  {
    availability: true,
    tag: "Embed on Unlimited Websites:",
    text: "Extend your reach by embedding Stomps across all your online platforms.",
  },
];
